

ALEXANDRA CANGE



<u>GitHub</u>



LinkedIn



alexandracange@gmail.com



+33 7 60077179



Portfolio



Wiesbaden, Germany

As an enthusiastic and results-oriented professional with an excitement for data and problem-solving, and with a background in operations, Supply Network Planner, a first short experience in IT and a certification in data sciences, I possess a unique blend of analytical, technical, and communication skills. Through my work in various industries and my extensive training in Python, SQL and BI Tools, I have honed my ability to extract meaningful insights from complex data sets and communicate those findings to organisation's all levels stakeholders.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

FRENCH - Native ENGLISH - Fluent GERMAN - Intermediate

TECHNICAL

CODING

Python, SQL, Javascript, HTML/CSS

DATA

Business Intelligence, Machine Learning, AI, AWS, API, ETL

BUSINESS

Excel, Project Management, Operations, Analytics, SAP S/4HANA

PERSONAL

Fast Learning Adaptability Problem-Solving Communication Customer Oriented

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SANVENCIA, WIESBADEN

SUPPLY NETWORK PLANNING

- Led inventory optimization, minimizing stockouts and excess stock by aligning levels with demand forecasts. Managed purchase orders and nurtured supplier relationships for timely deliveries through proactive communication on lead times and demand changes.
- Conducted insightful data analysis within the supply chain, identifying trends and preempting potential issues. Produced comprehensive reports on key metrics, facilitating informed decision-making. Additionally, demonstrated adeptness in ERP system utilization, ensuring accurate data input and leveraging system features to optimize overall supply chain processes.

JACK WOLFSKIN, IDSTEIN

IT RETAIL ANALYST

- · Ensured user support within the framework of the existing ERP and POS systems-SAP S4 & Advarics
- Administrated, developed and expanded the POS systems and connected systems.
- Supported all value-added processes with the aim of effective and efficient operation and the development of a modern organization.
- Determined requirements in cooperation with the specialist departments regarding extensions and adaptations of the POS systems and organizational processes.
- Actively monitoring data hygiene end to end along interfaces and systems.
- Key contact for departments creating and consuming POS related data. Communication hub for all POS related topics.

VIU EYEWEAR, MUNICH

SENIOR OPERATIONS MANAGER

04.2021 - 05.2022

09.2023 - Present

05.2023 - 07.2023

- Directed and oversaw staff of 25+ employee, designing schedules to meet the needs of the department as well as the needs of employees.
- Implemented a new inventory analysing system resulting saving 20% of spent time.

SWQ (Shipping, Warehouse, Quality Control) MANAGER

01.2020 - 03.2021

- Maintained detailed records of stocks, incoming goods and shipments.
- Evaluated productivity, implemented new processes and tracking processes systems resulting a better organisation and KPIs.

SHIPPING SUPERVISOR

01.2019 - 12.2019

- Supervised up to 10 shipping employees.
- Ensured all outbound orders are processed within 1.5 day.

OPERATIONS SPECIALIST

10.2017 - 12.2018

• Assisted to company goals and operational excellence.

EDUCATION

DATA SCIENCES

WBS Coding School 09.2022 - 01.2023

- Project Based
- Practice oriented
- Collaborative coding training

COMMERCE AND INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS

Public University Orléans, France 09.2013 - 07.2016

- Languages
- International Commerce
- International Management

PROJECTS

BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE:

• Business Customers Analysis (*Dashboard*)

DEEP LEARNING:

• Spotify Popularity Prediction (*Presentation*)

MACHINE LEARNING:

- Playlist Creation (*Presentation*)
- Movie Recommender (<u>App</u>)

DATA ENGINEERING:

• E-Scooter Company Advices (<u>Medium Post</u>)

DATA QUALITY:

• Tech E-Commerce Data (*Notebook*)